When we're first, gosh, mom's feeling that.
And we'll have the invocation by seeking
to the all Episcopal stretch, Ms. K.
Let us pray.
Almighty God, our heavenly Father, send down upon those
who hold office in this city, the spirit of wisdom,
charity, and justice, that with steadfast purpose,
they may faithfully serve in their office
to promote the well-being of all people through Jesus Christ
our Lord, Amen.
All right, number four, public input
or unscheduled personal appearances.
Five, action item, consent agenda.
Staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
Hi.
Number eight, acknowledgement, and a permit.
Number WL005-821-0366 for construction.
The 5,870 linear feet, the 12 inch HDPE.
Yes, or so, this is just the acknowledgement of the permit.
We received from DEQ, so it was part of the permit.
We get from them, we have to acknowledge, and at the next meeting.
So, I'm just excited everybody now.
So we don't have to do anything.
No, sir.
All right, this will be, if this will go down 69A,
and it will also come down from Rockdale Road
right there, so about the College Farm.
Okay.
Thank you.
Nine, action item.
They must write for my plane for Pinsco Project Relicency.
So this is with DWT.
It's additional bill that we've been working with them
on the study plan document.
And the initial study report that GRDA has been doing
is requested by FERC, which is related to the relicensing.
And as you all know, this relicensing, once it goes into effect,
will be in effect for potentially up to 50 years.
So the outcome of this report and the license that may or may not be
issues to GRDA is extremely important.
to Miami. And this initial study report is really possibly one of our last opportunities
to get our feedback on the record with FERC and with GRDA on any concerns that the city
would have related to the license and potentially the raising of Grand Lake, which is part
of the request that GRDA has made to raise the lake by an additional two feet. So part of the
study that's being done is the economic impact that that would have on anyone up streams, specifically
here in Ottawa County, and any infrastructure impact that that would have. So this has been really
an extensive study on the hydrologic reports. And so again we've had some really great team
members with DWT and making sure that we understand the studies, we understand the long-term
impact and that we document those appropriately for FERC. So again this is one of additional
bills to come as we've been working on this throughout the month of October. So this bill is actually
for the end of September. It's on the council tonight for approval and again I don't think this
is an opportunity where we'd be able to step away and not pay them for work that they were contracted
to perform and have performed on our behalf.
I'll vote in a second. Can I ask a question? Of course. Could we, at some point, once we kind
of get through this response type period and whatever? Could we have some kind of a,
oh, just an informational session with just a summary, maybe of an hour, hour and a half, two hours.
It folks want to come and listen. I know we worry about stepping away from the citizens and
stepping away from what we've taken on so many years ago and we also worry maybe the wrong
word, but we kind of feel like we're darned if we do and darned if we don't. So I was wondering
about, let's some citizens in this room and actually discuss it with them and try and garnish
some feet.
So that we don't maybe feel like we're on an island.
I think the outcome once they finalize our response to this initial study report, I think that would be the perfect opportunity,
which they're going to be wrapping that up here in November.
So maybe around the first of December-ish somewhere there that would be a perfect time to pull everyone together and really kind of go through the concerns that have been outlined in that report.
Cool.
Hi.
10 of the new business of any of those residents that are posting of this agenda,
11 trustee community announcements, and 12 adjournment.